{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732325774","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732325772"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 6599443d-7b3a-4329-9355-8ca3fb9eff03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732333812","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732333812"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 6599443d-7b3a-4329-9355-8ca3fb9eff03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_10_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732353964","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732353964"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 59aeae4f-c3c8-43ad-9988-8f21989df77b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ziwe_mayowe_maharagwe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732357009","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732357008"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 59aeae4f-c3c8-43ad-9988-8f21989df77b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_ziwe_mayowe_maharagwe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732379417","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732379416"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" ab2ae641-3d7a-4a7d-aad6-d406dbc9f7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ziwe_mayowe_maharagwe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732386081","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732386081"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" ab2ae641-3d7a-4a7d-aad6-d406dbc9f7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" jiwe_usichukuwe_mkewe_jiwe"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732392752","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732392751"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" ab2ae641-3d7a-4a7d-aad6-d406dbc9f7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" usiwe_niwe_mkongwe_usiwe"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732399400","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732399398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" ab2ae641-3d7a-4a7d-aad6-d406dbc9f7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" wewe_mumewe_wewe_usiwe"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732406070","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732406070"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" ab2ae641-3d7a-4a7d-aad6-d406dbc9f7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" usiwe_wenyewe_ngwe_usiwe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732412680","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732412679"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" ab2ae641-3d7a-4a7d-aad6-d406dbc9f7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" mwanawe_niwe_mwanawe_magozwe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732419308","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732419308"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" ab2ae641-3d7a-4a7d-aad6-d406dbc9f7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" mawe_mawe_mkwewe_jiwe"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732425930","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732425929"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" ab2ae641-3d7a-4a7d-aad6-d406dbc9f7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" wenyewe_mkewe_wenyewe_mumewe"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732432538","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732432538"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" ab2ae641-3d7a-4a7d-aad6-d406dbc9f7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" jiwe_jiwe_ngwe_mkongwe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732439180","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732439180"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" ab2ae641-3d7a-4a7d-aad6-d406dbc9f7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mawe_jiwe_mwishowe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732452325","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732452325"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" ab2ae641-3d7a-4a7d-aad6-d406dbc9f7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_mawe_jiwe_mwishowe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732457957","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732457957"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" ab2ae641-3d7a-4a7d-aad6-d406dbc9f7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.we.show.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_mawe_jiwe_mwishowe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732468484","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732468483"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 803ec2dd-8930-4fb8-8852-397f769c1c46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" usiwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIWE"," userResponse":" USIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732473888","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732473888"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 803ec2dd-8930-4fb8-8852-397f769c1c46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" usiwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732475454","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732475454"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 803ec2dd-8930-4fb8-8852-397f769c1c46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEWE"," userResponse":" MKEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732484570","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732484570"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 803ec2dd-8930-4fb8-8852-397f769c1c46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEWE"," userResponse":" MKEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732486140","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732486140"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 803ec2dd-8930-4fb8-8852-397f769c1c46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wanawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWE"," userResponse":" WANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732490680","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732490680"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 803ec2dd-8930-4fb8-8852-397f769c1c46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wanawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732492246","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732492246"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 803ec2dd-8930-4fb8-8852-397f769c1c46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkwewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKWEWE"," userResponse":" MKWEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732496420","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732496419"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 803ec2dd-8930-4fb8-8852-397f769c1c46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkwewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKWEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732497974","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732497974"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 803ec2dd-8930-4fb8-8852-397f769c1c46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIWE"," userResponse":" KIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732501038","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732501038"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 803ec2dd-8930-4fb8-8852-397f769c1c46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732502610","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732502610"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 803ec2dd-8930-4fb8-8852-397f769c1c46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkongwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONGWE"," userResponse":" MKONGWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732507464","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732507464"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 803ec2dd-8930-4fb8-8852-397f769c1c46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkongwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONGWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732509023","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732509023"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 803ec2dd-8930-4fb8-8852-397f769c1c46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwenyewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732513243","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732513242"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 803ec2dd-8930-4fb8-8852-397f769c1c46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwenyewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732514807","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732514806"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 803ec2dd-8930-4fb8-8852-397f769c1c46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWE"," userResponse":" NAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732518275","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732518275"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 803ec2dd-8930-4fb8-8852-397f769c1c46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732519832","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732519832"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 803ec2dd-8930-4fb8-8852-397f769c1c46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yowe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOWE"," userResponse":" YOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732523483","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732523481"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 803ec2dd-8930-4fb8-8852-397f769c1c46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yowe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732525067","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732525067"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 803ec2dd-8930-4fb8-8852-397f769c1c46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wenyewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYEWE"," userResponse":" WENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732528702","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732528702"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 803ec2dd-8930-4fb8-8852-397f769c1c46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wenyewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732530725","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732530724"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 803ec2dd-8930-4fb8-8852-397f769c1c46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" wenyewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732530879","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732530879"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 803ec2dd-8930-4fb8-8852-397f769c1c46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wenyewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732536494","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732536493"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201152"," gameId":" 803ec2dd-8930-4fb8-8852-397f769c1c46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" wenyewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}